### **Javier González Bodas**

02/08/1993

gonzalezbodasjavier@yahoo.es +34 695068361 Graduated in 2016 with a degree in Computer Engineering and currently working in the consulting sector. Experience in different technologies within the sector such as: Java and PHP as well as self-trained for personal projects on: JavaScript and Python.



## **Academic training**

#### 2011-2016 Degree in Computer Engineering

Escuela Técnica Superior de Ingenieros Informáticos Universidad Politécnica de Madrid

# **Experience**

#### Software Developer in atSistemas

Abril de 2021 – Actually

- Integrations Development (PHP, MariaDB, HTML/CSS, JavaScript, Docker)
- Control Version Tools (Git)
- Deployment tools (Jenkins)

#### May 2018 – Actually

- BBDD Scripts Development (PL/SQL).
- CRM Application Development (Java, Smart Client, Eclipse).
- Control Version Tools (SVN, PVCS).

#### • IT Engineer in Ericsson

August 2017 – May 2018

- BBDD Scripts Development (PL/SQL).
- CRM Application Development (Java, Smart Client, Eclipse).
- Control Version Tools (SVN, PVCS).

#### SAS Consultant in M2C Consulting & Procedures

June 2016 - June 2017

- Process Automation (Batch, Visual Basic).
- Data Analisis and Extraction, and Reporting (BOs ,SAS, Excel, Access).

## Languages

**English:** First Certificate in English (FCE)

Spanish: Native

# **Knowledge and Aptitudes**

Java (Amdocs Smart Client)
Development environments management (Eclipse)
Relational database language (SQL, PL/SQL)
PHP
Docker
JavaScript (jQuery, React)
Web design (HTML, CSS3, Bootstrap)
Python

## **Online Courses**

Python para Android, iOS, Windows, Linux y MAC - Desde Cero - Udemy

Curso de Spring Boot 2: Spring MVC+Thymeleaf+MySQL 8 (2020) - Udemy

### **Social Media**

**Personal Page:** https://javibodas.github.io **Github:** https://github.com/javibodas **LinkedIn:** Javier González Bodas